looking for a like new home with a pool
without the new home price welcome to
this stunning luxury listing in the
highly sought after community of bellat
tra in Nolanville
[Music]
Texas with so many upgrades and an
unbeatable location this home is a musty
so let's
[Music]
go this beautifully crafted four bedroom
2 and 1 half bath custombuilt home
offers Elegance space and thoughtful
[Music]
design featuring solidwood Cabinetry
travine tile floors plush carpeting in
the bedrooms every detail has been
meticulously designed for comfort and
style
[Music]
this Gourmet Kitchen was completely
renovated in 2022 with two-toned painted
cabinets allnew quartz counter tops new
fixtures a new sink and beautiful
stainless steel appliances including
this gas range I love this kitchen what
do you think can you see yourself here
[Music]
[Applause]
soaring 12T ceilings crown molding and a
welcoming front entryway with a barrel
ceiling and recess lighting create an
inviting
[Music]
atmosphere the fourth bedroom ideal as a
study showcases a beautiful coffered
ceiling the split bedroom layout ensures
privacy with secondary bedrooms separate
from the oversized Master
[Music]
Suite the primary Retreat features
private patio access and a luxurious
onsweet bath with dual vanities a Jetta
tub and marble surround shower
electric Shades in the main living
spaces provide effortless light control
and added convenience solar screens on
exterior windows enhance Energy
Efficiency
[Music]
step outside to your backyard Oasis
complete with an updated pool Serene
waterfall and plenty of space to relax
and
[Music]
unwind the garage has been upgraded with
brand new epoxy flooring and a newly
installed garage door adding both Style
and
durability situated on a spacious corner
lot spanning one4 of an acre this home
boasts breathtaking curb
[Music]
appeal located in colen is this home
offers luxury comfort and Resort style
living don't miss your chance to make it
yours well that wraps up our tour of
this beautiful home in Bella Chara if
you're looking to relocate to the
central Texas area be sure to scan the
QR code on the screen to download my
free relocation guide and if you'd like
a private tour of this home or any more
information on the area you can find all
my contact information below till next
time